{

    "question": "Who founded University College London?",
    "answer": "Jeremy Bentham",
    "options": ["Charles Darwin", "Jeremy Bentham", "Isaac Newton", "William Shakespeare", "Albert Einstein"]
},
{

    "question": "In what year was UCL established?",
    "answer": "1826",
    "options": ["1826", "1939", "1865", "1790", "1901"]
},
{

    "question": "What is the motto of UCL?",
    "answer": "Scientia et Labore",
    "options": ["Lux et Veritas", "In Hoc Signo Vinces", "Sapere Aude", "Scientia et Labore", "Deo Juvante"]
},
{

    "question": "Which famous philosopher taught at UCL?",
    "answer": "Karl Marx",
    "options": ["Socrates", "Aristotle", "Plato", "Friedrich Nietzsche", "Karl Marx"]
},
{

    "question": "Who is the current Provost of UCL?",
    "answer": "David Price",
    "options": ["Richard Horton", "David Price", "Jeremy Farrar", "Patrick Vallance", "Mark Walport"]
},
{

    "question": "Which UCL constituent college specializes in medical sciences?",
    "answer": "UCL Faculty of Medical Sciences",
    "options": ["UCL School of Slavonic and East European Studies", "UCL Institute of Education", "UCL Faculty of Laws", "UCL Faculty of Engineering Science", "UCL Faculty of Medical Sciences"]
},
{

    "question": "What is the name of UCL's student union?",
    "answer": "UCLSU",
    "options": ["UCL Union", "UCLU", "UCLSU", "UCL Student Life", "UCL Campus Life"]
},
{

    "question": "What is the name of UCL's main library?",
    "answer": "The UCL Main Library",
    "options": ["Senate House Library", "British Library", "UCL Library Services", "The Maughan Library", "The UCL Main Library"]
},
{

    "question": "Which famous writer studied at UCL?",
    "answer": "Virginia Woolf",
    "options": ["Virginia Woolf", "Charles Dickens", "William Shakespeare", "Jane Austen", "Oscar Wilde"]
},
{

    "question": "Which famous museum is located on UCL's campus?",
    "answer": "The Petrie Museum of Egyptian Archaeology",
    "options": ["British Museum", "Science Museum", "Natural History Museum", "Victoria and Albert Museum", "The Petrie Museum of Egyptian Archaeology"]
             }
    
 